Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor/Executive Vice President (Borowitz) RG.6.0.7
New York University Archives
- Series XII: Student Activities
  - Advisement & Counseling Study Group on Committee Work, Jan 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Advisement& Counseling Study Group on Committee Work, Feb 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Advisement & Guidance, Jul 1970-Oct 1972 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Athletics, Sports, Jul 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Attrition, Drop-Outs, Nov 1971-Oct 1976 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Committee on the Quality of Student Life, Jul 1972-Sep 1976 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Commuting Students, Jun 1974-May 1975 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Credit for Voluntary Work, Sep 1970-Nov 1972 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Degrees and Diplomas, Dec 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Disciplinary Action, Oct 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Dormitories, Sep 1974-May 1976 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Dormitories, Jan 1972-May 1974 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225015 2
  - Dormitories, Nov 1967-Nov 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Dormitories Other Than NYU, May 1970-Jun 1973 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Dormitories, Reports and Statistics, Mar 1972-1975 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Drugs, Nov 1974-May 1975 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Exchange Programs, German Students, Oct 1973-Apr 1974 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Exchange Programs & NYU Abroad, Sep 1974-Oct 1975 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Exchange Programs & NYU Abroad, Oct 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aid, Sep 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Financial Aid, Nov 1970-Jul 1975 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Sep 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Jan 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Oct 1974-Jun 1975 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Sep 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Sep 1972-Aug 1973 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid, HEOP, Sep 1971-Aug 1972 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid, Guaranteed Student Loan Program, Dec 1974-Feb 1976 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Financial Aid, Martin Luther King Jr. Program, Jan 1973-Jan 1977 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Financial Aid, Martin Luther King Jr. Program, Apr 1971-Nov 1972 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid, Press Coverage, Other Printed Materials, May 1970-Apr 1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225016 0
  - Financial Aid, Scholarships, Sep 1974-May 1976 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Financial Aid, Scholarships, Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Financial Aid, Scholarships, Jan 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid, Scholarships, May 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Fraternities, Jan 1973-Jan 1975 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities, May 1971-Dec 1972 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Freshmen, Oct 1971-Sep 1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Handicapped Students, Mar 1974-Jun 1975 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Health Services, Jul 1972-Aug 1975 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Identification Cards, Oct 1973 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - International Students, International Student Center, Jul 1971-Sep 1976 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Loeb Student Center, Mar 1971-Feb 1977 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Orientation, Apr 1975-Oct 1976 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Placement Services, Dec 1970-Nov 1976 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Placement Services, Annual Placement Reports, 1971-1972, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Recommendations, Jun 1972-Jan 1975 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Recruitment, Jun 1972-Nov 1976 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Registrar, Correspondence, Oct 1974-Mar 1977 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Registrar, Correspondence, Sep 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Religious Groups, Sep 1973-Oct 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225017 8
  - ROTC, Jan 1975-Oct 1975 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - ROTC, Apr 1970-Dec 1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore Entrance Proposal, May 1972-Jan 1976 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Jan 1975-Nov 1976 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Sep 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Sep 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Jan 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Feb 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Budget & Financial Matters, Sep 1974-Oct 1975 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Budget & Financial Matters, May 1972-Jun 1974 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, Weekend Emergency Duty Assignment, Oct 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Registrar, Correspondence, Jan 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Registrar, Student Enrollment Reports, Jul 1970-Mar 1977 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Registrar, Interim Enrollment Reports, Sep 1974-Mar 1977 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Registrar, Interim Enrollment Reports, Jan 1971-Jul 1974 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Registration Improvement Program, Oct 1975-Sep 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225018 6
  - Student Correspondence, Misc, Jan 1972-Aug1973 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Student Employment, Oct 1974-Dec 1976 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations, Feb 1973-Jan 1976 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations, Feb 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Student Participation, Jun 1970-Dec 1973 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Student Personality, Feb 1970-Feb 1971 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Student Publications, Oct 1973-May 1975 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Student Records (Federal Family Education Rights & Privacy Act of 1974 [H.R.69]), Buckley Amendment/PL93-380 (Access to Student Records), Feb 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Student Records (Federal Family Education Rights & Privacy Act of 1974 [H.R.69]), Buckley Amendment/PL93-380 (Access to Student Records), Jan 1975 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Student Records (Federal Family Education Rights & Privacy Act of 1974 [H.R.69]), Buckley Amendment/PL93-380 (Access to Student Records), Aug 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Student Typology, Oct 1970-Apr 1971 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Student Views, Nov 1970-Aug 1974 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Student Views, Jan 1969-Jun 1970 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Transfer Students, Feb 1974-Nov 1975 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Tuition and Fees, Nov 1974-Jul 1976 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Tuition and Fees, May 1971-May 1974 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - University Scholars Program, Dec 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Veterans Affairs, Jun 1972-Jan 1976 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Visiting Student Program & Junior Year in New York, Sep 1972-Sep 1974 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Work Study, Internships, Oct 1970-Jan 1976 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED MATERIALS - Cambodian Crisis, 1970 (Box 83)